What have the last 24 hours been like
for you? Obviously waking up yesterday
and not knowing where you're going to be
spending the next whatever decade of
your life and now all of a sudden you're
here.
>> Yeah. Um it's been a great experience.
Like a lot of moving around like being
in Pittsburgh and going to different
events, the red carpet then the green
room and coming out here. But um it's
been incredible. I'm happy to be here.
>> Were you able to get any sleep last
night or like what was it?
>> A little bit. I was thinking about it a
lot but I was able to sleep a little
bit.
What were your impressions just walking
through the building, especially that
players entrance and just what's kind of
going through your mind as you see the
numbers and names of the people played
in for this team?
>> Yeah. Uh I know this team has a lot of
history. Um and it's been awesome to to
kind of see that displayed as you walk
through the building and um I'm just
happy to get in and get to work.
>> How much did you know about that growing
up not too far away from here?
>> Um I know a little bit. Um, I was really
young when we were as a family a Bears
team, but um, I'm excited to learn more.
Were
>> you a Colts guy growing up? Obviously.
>> Yeah, when we moved down to
Indianapolis, we were Colts, but still
had the Bears in there somewhere.
>> Last night you said that you connected
with the Bears at the combine in a in an
interview. What exact expand on that?
What what exactly about the interview
was positive?
>> Yeah, I mean, uh, overall I felt like
there was a lot of positive energy going
around. Um, it felt easy. It was great
to talk to the team. Like they had a lot
of guys in there. Um and then me sitting
in like the one chair that's kind of
standing out, but um they're just asking
some background questions, talking
through some film. Then they have me get
on the whiteboard a little bit.
>> You said yesterday that you were a
little almost like surprised like I know
you had the meeting with them at the
combine and then not a whole ton of
connection with them in between then and
when you were drafted. Did you think you
were go was there somewhere on the board
that you had circled that you thought
you'd be going before you wind up at 25
here? Um overall like we had ideas so
wherever I might go but um in the moment
I kind of just stayed calm and and
prayed I hope I got to the right spot
and I think this was the right spot. So
I mean through that process like we
talked at the combine um they showed
their interest. I heard a lot from them
like through other people and then it
all worked out in the end. when you were
making a decision to transfer from
Purdue to Oregon, what were you
envisioning for that that next year? And
and what do you in retrospect, what do
you think you accomplished by by making
that move?
>> Um, I mean, going into that that year at
Oregon, um, I had the goal set that I
want to go one year and go. Um, so going
through that and I wanted to to put
everything I could into that knowing
that, um, if I did decide to stay, it
was the right decision. If I decided to
leave, I put everything in. So, I made
the right choice going to Oregon. Um,
and what was the the second part of your
question?
>> What do you think you accomplished when
you look back on your year in Oregon?
>> Uh, I think I accomplished a lot. I know
we came up short, um, but I made some
great connections with those coaches and
those teammates that I'll probably have
rest of my life.
>> It sound It sounded like they coached
you very hard at Oregon. Even uh even
some of the talks they had with you kind
of recruiting you to transfer there,
they were pretty tough on you. um what
made you receptive to that and how do
you think that made you better?
>> Um in the recruiting process like out of
out of high school and transferring in
college um it's more like the player
picks. So a lot of people are I guess
like sugar coating it or trying to
trying to talk you up and uh talking
with H talking with Lanning like they
didn't sugarcoat anything. They told me
exactly like we think you're a good
player. This is what you need to work
on. This is how we can get you better.
This is how we develop guys in the past.
Um, and to see those examples and see
how they had a plan for me, um, made a
very easy decision.
>> Dylan, what do you remember, uh, from
learning under Jake Gilbert? He was
saying that, uh, even as in youth
football, you were out running guys in
high school.
>> Um, Coach Gilbert always liked talking
about TNTs, that tank, no talents. So,
always it's a effort and attitude. So, I
mean, effort, just running the ball is
is one thing that everyone can do,
doesn't matter what your talent level
is. So he also said that your dad uh
used to tell you um skate to where the
puck is going to be. You remember that
and what that means your interpretation?
>> Um I don't remember it as much. My idea
is that it's probably like more of a
feel for the game. So how's how's the
how's the pocket moving? What are they
trying to attack? Um and just be
aggressive to the point of attack.
>> You talked about the the studies you put
into your role and other roles on the
defense. Where does your passion for
football come from? What makes you put
in the work that you do for this game?
>> It starts with that that little kid, the
four-year-old me looking up that TV,
being like, "Hey, it's going to be me
out there." Um, but then it goes into to
seeing my family and my brothers do it.
Um, see my parents, how they work in
their businesses. And, uh, really
watching my brothers out there on the
field, wanting to be out there with
them. Um, and then I'm I'm someone I
think like if I if I really love
something, I'm going to put all my
energy, all my work into it. Are are you
able to use that kind of perspective of
understanding and appreciating this
moment today and last night?
>> Yes. Yeah. I know this is once a
lifetime moment, so you just got to you
got to take it all in and u just enjoy
it.
>> What do you remember your football
acumen in playing that rover role at
Oregon? How did that, I guess, expand
your football IQ and prepare you to for
what you're about to do in the NFL and
just the vers like changing the
versatility or like strengthening the
versatility of your game?
>> Yeah. Um that position really allows you
to play fast. you you uh can be
aggressive in the run game because a lot
of times um just the distance I'm off
from the line of scrimmage, I'm I'm the
extra unblocked defender. Um and then
the pass game that playing that rover
roll, you're kind of that middle of the
field. So you're what what the offense
most likely like like once the target a
lot of times. So um that just allowed me
a lot more opportunities to get around
the ball, get more experience and uh
just think about what the offense is
trying what they're showing me in their
formations and or situations and what
they're trying to attack. polls up last
night that like the way you play is what
it takes the oxygen out of an offense.
Um, is there a play that you remember
from college that like you felt that
energy? You felt that same thing like
the play it just like completely
decimated what they were doing?
>> Um,
I mean, one of them is the the Penn
State game just at the end of the game.
Um just to I mean it's a white out game,
college game day and the stadium's going
super loud, double overtime and to to
get the pick and then everything just
goes silent and I could hear my all the
Oregon fans and and my family kind of
yelling up in the stands. So that one
was awesome.
>> Dylan, how do you calculate when to take
risk as a defender and when to just stay
more sound and responsibility?
>> Um I think that just comes more with
experience. So, experience watching the
game, experience playing uh going
against certain teams, certain offenses,
and uh playing in different defensive
schemes and the and trusting your guys
around you. Um so, I can't tell you like
this, I do that. Another situation, you
do this. It's more of just a feel for
it.
>> Dude, Dylan, going back to going back to
your family, how do you think being the
youngest of three brothers kind of
shaped you athletically, maybe as a
competitor? It
>> definitely helped me. like they were
they were a good amount of years older
than me. So to see what they're doing,
they were kind of just teaching it,
applying it to me. So I got it at a much
younger age than other people would have
gotten it or that they got at their age.
Um so I feel like that just spread up my
u development and allowed me to
>> always at games, always at the gym, just
always
>> be what do you what do you remember
about facing Coulson
when you were at Purdue?
Um,
I know that they won and
>> they won a lot of games.
>> Yes, they won a lot of games. Um, but
no, he's an extremely talented player. I
didn't get to to match up with him
specifically in that game because of our
defensive scheme, but I know he's a
great player.
>> And JJ McCarthy, too. He's somebody
who's now in your division and depending
on what happens there may start for
them. What do you do you have any memory
of of him? Uh,
not a whole lot, but I I can't wait to
to face him again.
>> Having been in the Pacific Northwest,
how much did you watch Kobe Bryant and
now getting a chance to play alongside
him and learn from him here with the
Bears?
>> Uh, I wasn't able to watch a whole lot
of him, but I'm I'm very excited to to
get the chance to to learn from him and
and to work with him.
>> Did you have a favorite player growing
up or somebody you tried to emulate your
game after?
Uh, I really like I liked watching or
going back and watching once I was
older. Um, like Troy Palmer, Ed Reed.
Um, and then currently I like I watch
various players around the league. So, I
like to kind of like take a little bit
um, see where I can learn something and
then kind of make it my own.
>> Have you heard from any of your new
teammates over the last 24 hours?
>> Yeah, Colston. Coloulston text me I
think right away. Um, I'm sure someone
else has texted me. I haven't been able
to go through them all. What Colston
tell you?
>> He was just like, "Yo, glad to have you
on the team. Can't wait to get to work.
Let me know if you need anything."
>> What's been your interaction so far with
either Ben or or Dennis Allen?
>> Yeah, I just had a few meetings with
them. It was great meeting just sitting
down talking about um how they see my
role in the team and and what they think
we can do.